[{"answer": "The bus is the single stupidest, fattest, slowest, most despised vehicle on the road. Isn't it? You ever notice when you get behind the bus, people in your car go 'what are you doing? get away, come on.' The back of the bus is like an eclipse isn't it? people are just like 'the sun, where's the sun?' It's like this huge metal ass taking up the whole wind shield of your car. When it pulls out it even sounds like a fat uncle trying to get out of a sofa. ", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stand-In.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "It's not good", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I'm bored. She's boring, I'm boring, we're both boring. We got out to eat, we both read newspapers", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stand-In.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "No. Lunch we read, dinner we read", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Well at breakfast everybody reads", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stand-In.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "You read during lunch", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Oh, well", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stand-In.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Ya, what's there to talk about", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "There's nothing to talk about", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stand-In.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Well at least you and I are talking about how there's nothing to talk about", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Ya, what's there to talk about", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stand-In.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Why don't you talk to her about how there's nothing to talk about", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Well at least you and I are talking about how there's nothing to talk about", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stand-In.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "She knows there is nothing to talk about", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Why don't you talk to her about how there's nothing to talk about", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stand-In.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "At least you'll be talking", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " That's good work", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stand-In.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " I'm not really going away, I told you I'd be back every other weekend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "..so uh she's just sitting there and a uh Pachyderm, you remember the derm. He says uh, I'm gonna go up to her. So we uh he uh picks up the two pieces of  pizza and uh the uh and then they're steaming hot and they're burning his hands see so he... he's juggling em  he's jugglin em, jus throwing them up in the air and just as he gets up to her down they go.  Well we all just lost it.  It was really, really, funny.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stand-In.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Hey my friend how you doing", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Do I know him", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stand-In.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "If you were a woman would you go out with him", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "If I was a woman I'd be down at the dock waiting for the fleet to come in", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stand-In.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "all right.", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Yes, I am", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stand-In.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I don't see any way around it", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "my friend's wife told me it's all my fault. She said since my visit he's taken a turn for the worse", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stand-In.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " Yes I told him the Pachyderm story", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Why not", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stand-In.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I thought we were going to spend the day together", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "No, no I do. You know it's just..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stand-In.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " No he's not right. my friend is not right! all right I'm canceling the fathe", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Oh, I'm sorry, Oh. What a story", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stand-In.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Oh that is one of the funniest stories I've ever heard", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "You know, you really are beautiful my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stand-In.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Good night", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stand-In.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Oh, the date. The date", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": " He what", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stand-In.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "He took what out", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Yea", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stand-In.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "It", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "It", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stand-In.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Out", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "So she's just sitting there, she's having a pleasant conversation... and all of a sudden", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stand-In.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "It", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "I'm very disappointed to here you talk like that. You still don't know what makes me tick", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stand-In.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "What are you doing", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Nah, rock flies right through paper", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stand-In.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": " Nothing beats rock", "qsentId": 50}]